Jewish Federation of Greater Hartford Collection 0006.023.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Audiotape Series I:
  - Poland radio, Passover, April. 7, 1982 (Box 1)
- Series XL: Scrapbooks
  - 1960 (Box 40)
  - 1967 (Box 40)
  - 1967 Israel Emergency fund (Box 40)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 40)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 40)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 40)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 40)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - 1973 (Box 40)
  - 1974 (Box 40)
  - 1978 (Box 40)
  - 1978 (Box 40)
  - April 1976-Sept. 1976 (Box 40)
  - March 1977-March 1978 (Box 40)
  - March 1978-March 1979 (Box 40)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - May-81, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Women's Division 1976-1977 (Box 40)
  - Women's Division 1977-1978 (Box 40)
  - Women's Division 1978 (Box 40)
- Series XIL: Newspaper Clippings
  - 1982-1983 clippings (Box 41)
  - 1982-1984 (Box 41)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 41)
  - 1986 (Box 41)
  - 1986-1986 (Box 41)
  - 1987 (Box 41)
  - 1987 (Box 41)
  - 1987 (Box 41)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 41)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - 1989-1990, 1989-1991 (Box 41)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 41)
  - 1990-1991 and 1991-1992, 1990-1992 (Box 41)
  - 1992 Gala (Box 41)
- Photo Series I: Annual Campaign: Leadership; Young Leadership
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Composite: Officers and Directors of United Jewish Charities, 1922 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Dodd, Christopher, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1980 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Dayan, Moshe, 1960s-1980s, 1960-1980 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Eban, Abba, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Grasso, Ella, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Kennelly, Barbara, 1980, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Lieberman, Joseph, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Meir, Golde, 1940s-1950s, 1940-1959 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with O'Neill, Governor William, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Peres, Shimon, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Ribicoff, Abraham, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Ullmann, Liv, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Weiker, Lowell, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership with Wiesel, Elie, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1950s-60s, 1950-1969 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Individuals/Kessler, Irving, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Individuals/Siegal, Howard, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Individuals/Waldeman, Bernie and Bernice, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Individuals/Winkler, Mr. and Mrs. Jan, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Individuals/New Britain, 1950s-1960s, 1950-1959 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership, 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1977 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1978 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1984 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1985 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1986 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/1994 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership with Barbara Kennelly/1994 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/4 star event, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Young Leadership/Noll, Leigh, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Endowment Window/Builders Dinner, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Quarter Century Club, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual Campaign/Leadership/Day with Teddy Kollack, Mayor of Jerusalem, 1979 (Box 1)
- Photo Series II: Annual Campaign: Events, groups, volunteers, suburban campaigns
  - Annual Campaign/Agency Staff thank you, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Ambassador's Ball, 1960s-80s, 1960-1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Ambassador's ball, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Campaign cabinet meeting, undated (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Campaign cabinet, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Campaign cabinet, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Completion, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Dentists, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Dentists, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Dentists, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Groups, miscellaneous, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Retreat, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Sensational Sunday, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Single adults, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Single adults, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/Manchester, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/New Britain, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/Newington, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/Rockville, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/South Windsor, undated (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Suburban/Windsor, undated (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Thanks for giving dinner, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Volunteers, 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Volunteers/Gerber, Sonia1981 (Box 2)
  - Annual Campaign/Volunteers/Senior Adults, recognition, 1989 (Box 2)
- Photo Series III: Annual Campaign: Women's Division
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1960s-1970s,several folders, 1960-1979 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division/Business and Professional Women, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division/Business and Professional Women/phonathon, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division/Lion of Judah, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division/undated (Box 3)
  - Annual Campaign/Women's Division/Young Women, 1980s – 1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 3)
  - Check: file not here Young women, bowling party, 1994 (Box 3)
- Photo Series IV: Annual Campaign: Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 4)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 4)
- Photo Series V: Annual Campaign: Miscellaneous, 1980s
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1980s, several folders (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1987, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1986, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 5)
- Photo Series VI: Annual Campaign: Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1990s
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1990, several folders (Box 6)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1992-1993, several folders (Box 6)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Annual Campaign/Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 6)
- Photo Series VII: Annual Campaign: Box 7: SuperSunday 1970s-1980s
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1974 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1978 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1980 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1981 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1982 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1983 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1984 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1985 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1986 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1987 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1988 (Box 7)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1989 (Box 7)
- Photo Series VIII: Annual Campaign: SuperSunday 1991-1992
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1991 (Box 8)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1992 (Box 8)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1992 (Box 8)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/Collage from Federation book, 1990s (Box 8)
- Photo Series IX: Annual Campaign: SuperSunday 1993 –2000
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1993 (Box 9)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1994 (Box 9)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/Kef Korner, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1994 (Box 9)
  - Annual Campaign/SuperSunday/1995-2000 (Box 9)
  - Campaign/SuperSunday/undated (Box 9)
- OVERSIZE Campaign photos:
  - Box 1: Leadership with celebrities, undated
  - Box 2: Miscellaneous groups and events, undated
- Photo Series X: Administration
  - Administration/Buildings and grounds/Federation building, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Buildings and grounds/sculpture, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Endowment fund making scholarship grant to B'Nai Brith, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Families attending opening of Community Services Building, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff,1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff, 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff/Chanukah party, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff/Cooper, Don, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff/Matt, Karin, undated (Box 10)
  - Administration/Staff/Gottlieb, Bernie, undated (Box 10)
- Photo Series XI: Board of Directors
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Board Officers, 1980s-1990s, 1980-1990 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Group photographs, undated (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Presidents/Group photos, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors/Presidents/Individual portraits/photocopies, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Feltman, Philip, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Green, Louis, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Konover, Simon, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Siskin, Robert, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Stavis, Frank, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Suisman, Michael, undated (Box 11)
  - Board/of/Directors/Suisman, Richard, undated (Box 11)
- Photo Series XII: Beneficiary Agencies, Commission on Jewish Education, Community Calendar
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Federation homes, Bloomfield, undated (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Federation homes, Bloomfield/Bat Torah, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Federation homes, Bloomfield/Anniversaries/10th, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Federation Square, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Jewish Community Center, undated (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Jewish Family Services/Weiner, Phil, undated (Box 12)
  - Beneficiary Agencies/Schools, undated (Box 12)
  - Commission on Jewish Education, 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 12)
  - Commission on Jewish Education/Drescher, Yosefa, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Community Calendar, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Community Calendar, 1992 (Box 12)
- Photo Series XIII: Community Service Projects
  - Community Service Projects/Adult Day Care program, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Calendar Day, City Service Project, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Continuity Council, 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Continuity Grant/Adult Education Network, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Continuity Grant/Family education, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Continuity Grant/Parent Education Programs, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Couples Awareness, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Education, suburban, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Ethiopian Jewry, 1980s (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Ethiopian Jewry, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Family Expo, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Gulf War projects, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Habitat Harvarim, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Hartford Shalom, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Hartford Shalom, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Hartford Shalom, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Hartford Shalom, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Holocaust commemoration, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Holocaust commemoration, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Holocaust commemoration, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Holocaust commemoration, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Holocaust commemoration, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Intermarriage, programs about, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel/Missions/Misc, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel/Missions, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel/Missions, 2000s, 2000-2009 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel (France)/Missions/n.d., undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel 45, Fair and Walk, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel Independence Day, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel Program, early 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel Symposium, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israel today mission, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Israeli Festival, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Jerusalem Day in Hartford City Hall, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Jewish Awareness, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Jewish Spirituality through the Ages, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Literacy volunteers, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Older Adult committee, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Operation Manah, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Precious Legacy Exhibit at Atheneum, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Project Renewal, Sister City Afula, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Purim at Beth Israel, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry/March, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, Rally, Mary Travers, Performer, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, Rally, Christopher Dodd, speaker, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry, several folders of photographs, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry/Rally, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Soviet Jewry/new Americans, 1992 (Box 13)
  - For Soviet Jewry see also JCRC, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Synagogue-Federation dialog, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Teen Leadership, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Thank you America, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Youth programs, miscellaneous, undated (Box 13)
  - Community Service Projects/Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, undated (Box 13)
- Photo Series XIV: Community Service Projects: Walkathon
  - Community Service Projects/Walkathon, 1978, Israel at 30 (Box 14)
  - Community Service Projects/Walkathon, 1979, Israel at 31 (Box 14)
  - Community,Service,Projects/Walkathon, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Community,Service,Projects/Walkathon, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Community Service Projects/Walkathon, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Community,Service,Projects/Walkathon,1983 (Box 14)
  - Community,Service,Projects/Walkathon,1984 (Box 14)
  - Community Service Projects/Walkathon, 1986 (Box 14)
- Photo Series XV: Special Campaigns and Other Charities
  - Special Campaigns/Israel Emergency fund, undated (Box 15)
  - Special Campaigns/Operation Exodus, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Special Campaigns/Russian resettlement, 1970s-1990s, 1970-1999 (Box 15)
  - Special Campaigns/Suburban Campaigns, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Special Campaigns/Yom Kippur War, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Other charities/Council of Jewish Federations and United Jewish Appeal United Jewish Appeal, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 15)
  - Other charities/ United Jewish Appeal including David Ben Gurion, 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 15)
  - Other charities/ United Jewish Appeal, Miscellaneous, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 15)
  - Other charities/United Jewish Appeal/miscellaneous, undated (Box 15)
- Photo Series XVI: Jewish Community Relations Council (JCRC)
  - JCRC/Annual meeting, 1958 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Interfaith 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Legislative Activities, undated (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Legislative gathering/Gedenson, Sam, 1983 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Meeting with Yossi Olmert, 1994 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/September 11, 2001, response of JCRC (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Rallies and other events. Participants included Mary Travers, Senator Christopher Dodd and Governor William O'Neill, 1980s, undated (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Miscellaneous, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 16)
  - JCRC/Soviet Jewry/Grasso, Ella and Senator Henry Jackson, with Falkovich family, 1979 (Box 16)
- Photos Oversized: Board of Directors, Staff, etc
  - Borden, Abraham S., undated
  - Catler, Marvin, undated
  - Cohen, Harold, undated
  - Cooper, Don, undated
  - Feinstein, Arthur, undated
  - Feltman, Phil, undated
  - Fierberg, I. Martin, undated
  - Gamble, Harry, undated
  - Gotlieb, Bernard, undated
  - Kaplan, Bernard, undated
  - Kessler, Irving, undated
  - Konover, Simon, undated
  - Levine, I. Oscar, undated
  - Naboicheck, N. Aaron, undated
  - Neiditz, Dan, undated
  - Roskin, Samuel, undated
  - Roth, Louis K., undated
  - Rubenstein, Charles, undated
  - Savin, A. I., undated
  - Siskin, Robert, undated
  - Stavis, frank, undated
  - Stern, Francis E., undated
  - Suisman, Edward, undated
  - Suisman, Edward A., undated
  - Suisman, Michael, undated
  - Title, Melvin, undated
  - Composite: Officers and Directors of United Jewish Charities, 1922